Eh, sorry about the shower.
え、シャワーごめん
Did you take a shower?
シャワー行ってたの?
Yes, I was taking a shower.
うん、シャワー行ってました
Are you sweating?
汗かいたの?
Yeah.
うん
I think it was encouraging.
激励したと思うね
Hey, can I watch you take a shower?
ちょっとさ、シャワーを行くとこ見てていいの?
Yeah.
うん
sweat.
汗
While I was taking a shower like this,
こうやって自分でシャワー浴びているところ、
Is it worth it?
見合うことある?
do not have.
ない
How do you feel now?
今どんな気持ち?
noisy.
うるさい
By the way, what part of the body is most important to wash in the shower?
ちなみにさ、シャワーで体のどこに一番体を洗うのが大事なの?
No fun for regular people?
いつもの人にとっては楽しみはない?
Are you thinking of putting it around here for now?
とりあえずここら辺にかけると思ってるの?
You mean around here?
ここら辺って言うの?
No way.
うむねない
Are you saying no?
うむねないって言うの?
Boobs, boobs.
おっぱい、おっぱい
What's next?
その次は?
Next?
その次?
An arm?
腕とか?
An arm or something.
腕とか
What's next?
その次は?
Let's stop it already.
もうやめよう
Ah, maybe so.
ああ、そうなのかもしれない
how was your day?
今日はどうでしたか?
I'm sorry I took a shower earlier, but
前にシャワー浴びた時にごめんなさいけど、
Through individual photography.
一人一人の撮影を通して
Through shooting.
撮影を通して
How was it?
どうでしたか?
どうでした?
How was it?
どうでしたか?
That's not what I mean.
そういうことじゃないです
It's cute.
かわいいね
After all, it's done.
やっぱれてます
Hello.
どうもー
Thank you.
どうも
something?
何か?
Thank you.
どうも
Ah, something came in.
あ、何か入ってきちゃったね
Something has come in.
何か入ってきちゃった
Thank you.
どうも
I have something great to say.
すごい言いたそうなことある
picture?
え?
cute.
かわいい
I'm here again.
また来た
Look below.
見て下の方
It's cute.
かわいいです
Maybe it's already over.
もう終わったのかもしれない
Yeah.
うん
No way.
いやー
Shall we stop for once?
一回止めようか
stop?
止める?
Shall we stop for once?
一 回止めようか
I think I can't sleep at night with just my mouth.
お口だけじゃちょっと夜寝れないなと思って
Can't sleep at night?
夜寝れない?
Really.
ほんとに
I won't sleep anymore.
もう寝ない
I feel like I'm not completely satisfied yet.
まだ完全に満足しちゃってない感じですかね
I wish I had such a cute child.
こんなかわいい子いたらね
I can't be satisfied with just my mouth.
お口だけじゃ満足できない
Well, it's true that my lower body is sagging.
まあ確かに下半身がおろがらってますね
It looks like it just came out.
出したばっかになる
Is it okay?
いいっすか?
"Eh, okay?" he said again.
え、いいっすかってのもう一回口で
No, no, no, no.
いやいやいやいや
Tes?
て、てすか?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
picture?
え?
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
What a place?
なんてとこ?
picture?
え?
I told you to go to sleep earlier, what do you mean?
さっき寝てって言ったけど、なんてとこ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
picture?
え?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
I don't like it either.
俺も嫌だ
Come to think of it, the guy I was friends with earlier...
そういえば、さっき仲良いのしたやつ、
I can take it properly.
ちゃんと取れる
picture?
え?
What did you say?
えってしたんですか?
No, I won't be able to get through the new year if I don't do it.
いや、もうしないともう年越せない
picture?
え?
Even with these eyes, it would be dangerous if I went home like this.
この目はでも、このまま帰ったら危ないな
It might be news.
ニュースになるかも
picture?
え?
I'm sorry, um, but I think I was quite confused.
ちょっとごめんね、あのー、 まぁだいぶ困惑してたと思うんです
Yo.
よ
It ended there, so I guess it's over.
そ こで終わったんで、もう多分ね、
I think he was bathing in society on the way home.
帰りの社会で浴びてたと思うんですけど、
No, but just now, I lost my memory.
いやでもさっき、 さっき、 記憶喪失なっちゃった
Huh?
あれ?
Did something happen?
何かあった?
strange.
おかしい
I'll help you more.
もっとお助けするんで
body?
体?
Let's do it properly.
ちゃんとやってあげましょう
Properly, properly, properly.
ちゃんとちゃんとちゃんと
Here too, I have to do my best here.
ここも、なんかね、 ここしっかりあがんないと
It doesn't matter.
なんか関係ない
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
You can't go home, can you?
帰れないでしょ?
Stretch your arms out a little.
ちょっと脇を伸べて
I'm sweating.
汗かくっすもんね
汗かくる
The paper mache is amazing.
張り絵がすごい
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter.
関係ない関係ない
it doesn't matter?
関係ない?
Yeah.
うん
If you do this on top, it will look nicer.
上にこうやるときれいになるんですよ
It becomes beautiful from top to bottom, top to bottom like this.
上にこう、上下にこう、きれいになるんですよ
Are you being cleaned everywhere by a man?
男の人にどこもきれいにされてる?
Is it showing up?
現れてる?
picture?
え?
No way.
やだー
picture?
え?
Where where?
どこどこ?
picture?
え?
The top and bottom will be clean.
上下きれいになる
Let it flow once, let it flow once.
一回流す、一回流すね
She's such a beautiful child.
すごいきれいな子なのな
The air is bad.
空気悪いぞ
I'm aware.
気がついよー
I'm wondering if it's a little more there.
もうちょっと、そこねーのかっていう
It became clean.
きれいになった
It's clean now, but please clean it for me too.
きれいになったんだけど、 俺もきれいにしてください
Cleanly.
きれいに
If you don't clean it up, I won't be able to go home.
きれいにしてくれないと、もう帰れない
Can't go home?
帰れない?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうそう
May I?
いいですか?
I don't need to worry about it.
僕の方が気にしないでいいんで
Is it okay?
いいっすか?
Good
いいっす
mosquito?
か?
Good!
いい っ
Do you?
す か?
out
出
Can I do that?
して いい?
This is terrible, this is terrible
やばい、やばい、これ
too.
も
I ended up inside again.
また 中でちゃったけど
good?
よ かった?
Still inside.
まだ中で
Not good.
よくない
Isn't it good?
よくない?
I have to write it out again, properly.
もう一回書き出さないとね、ちゃんと
I want you to stay in this position for a while and clean me up a bit.
ちょっとこの体勢のままで、 ちょっと お掃除してあげてほしく
hand.
て
I was surprised today.
び っくりしたね、今日にね
Come in from the shower.
シャワーから入ってきてね
By the way, did you feel the sperm coming out inside?
ちなみに、この精子は中に出てる感じ分かった?
Yeah.
うん
What was it like?
どんな感じだった?
picture?
え?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
I feel like my heart is pounding.
なんかドキドキする感じ
Got it?
分かった?
Yeah.
うん
Did you stop pounding?
ドクドク打て止めた?
Yeah.
うん
In that state, in the final summary,
その状態で、最後終わった総括で、
What do you think about the shooting?
撮影の感想といった
In one word.
一言で言って
While peace.
ピースしながら
It was difficult.
大変でした
My feet tremble.
足プルプルする
Does it jiggle?
プルプルする?
real?
ほんと?
Which one is this?
これどれ?
real?
ほんと?
It's true, I'm shaking.
ほんとだ、震えてる
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
It's light.
軽くしてる
Then try again while doing the peace.
じゃあピースしながらもう一回
Yeah.
うん
I was told that I had to go through with it twice.
二回仲立ちされちゃいましたって
I was brokered twice.
二回仲立ちされちゃいました